<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
  <menu.start>
    <FR>Commencer</FR>
    <EN>Start</EN>
  </menu.start>
  <menu.quit>
    <FR>Quitter</FR>
    <EN>Back To Desktop</EN>
  </menu.quit>
  <menu.settings>
    <FR>Options</FR>
    <EN>Settings</EN>
  </menu.settings>
  <menu.about>
    <FR>À propos</FR>
    <EN>About</EN>
  </menu.about>
  <menu.yes>
    <FR>Oui</FR>
    <EN>Yes</EN>
  </menu.yes>
  <menu.no>
    <FR>Non</FR>
    <EN>No</EN>
  </menu.no>
  <menu.confirm>
    <FR>Voulez-vous vraiment quitter ?</FR>
    <EN>Are you sure you want to exit?</EN>
  </menu.confirm>
  <menu.back>
    <FR>Retour</FR>
    <EN>Back</EN>
  </menu.back>
  <menu.ok>
    <FR>OK</FR>
    <EN>OK</EN>
  </menu.ok>
  <menu.apply>
    <FR>Appliquer</FR>
    <EN>Apply</EN>
  </menu.apply>
  <about.desc>
    <FR>Cette démo a été entièrement réalisé par Johann Seys. Pour plus d'informations vous pouvez consulter la page du projet sur mon portfolio en cliquant sur le bouton internet en bas à droite. Vous pouvez également consulter mon profil LinkedIn en cliquant sur le bouton LinkedIn</FR>
    <EN>This demo is integrally made by Johann Seys. You can check out the project's page for more informations on my portfolio by clicking on the Internet icon. You can also check my LinkedIn profile by clicking on the LinkedIn button.</EN>
  </about.desc>
  <settings.language>
    <FR>Langue</FR>
    <EN>Language</EN>
  </settings.language>
  <settings.music>
    <FR>Musique</FR>
    <EN>Music</EN>
  </settings.music>
  <settings.effects>
    <FR>Effets</FR>
    <EN>Effects</EN>
  </settings.effects>
  <settings.audio>
    <FR>Son</FR>
    <EN>Audio</EN>
  </settings.audio>
  <intro.welcome>
    <FR>Bienvenue</FR>
    <EN>Welcome</EN>
  </intro.welcome>
  <helper.reinit>
    <FR>Reinitialiser</FR>
    <EN>Reset</EN>
  </helper.reinit>
  <helper.looktwice>
    <FR>Ne jugez rien au premier regard</FR>
    <EN>Don't judge anything you see at first sight</EN>
  </helper.looktwice>
  <helper.greenside>
    <FR>Le sage montre la lune, l'idiot regarde le doigt</FR>
    <EN>When the wise man points at the moon, the fool looks at the finger</EN>
  </helper.greenside>
  <helper.redside>
    <FR>Garder votre objectif en vue et vous l'atteindrez</FR>
    <EN>By watching where you want to go, you should end up reaching your goal</EN>
  </helper.redside>
  <helper.turnleft>
    <FR>Tournez à gauche</FR>
    <EN>Turn Left</EN>
  </helper.turnleft>
  <helper.fool>
    <FR>Donc... vous devez être l'idiot... mmm</FR>
    <EN>So... you're the fool I guess... huh...</EN>
  </helper.fool>
  <helper.angle>
    <FR>Un problème peut être abordé par différents angles</FR>
    <EN>A problem can be approached from various angles</EN>
  </helper.angle>
  <helper.stairs>
    <FR>Toutes les solutions ne se présentent pas à nous comme on le voudrait</FR>
    <EN>Every solutions don't come to us as we would like to</EN>
  </helper.stairs>
  <helper.lightmaze>
    <FR>Tous les feux doivent être au vert</FR>
    <EN>All the lights shall be green</EN>
  </helper.lightmaze>
  <helper.lighttips>
    <FR>Votre dernier mouvement doit se passer ici</FR>
    <EN>If you're not ending with that room, you're doing it wrong</EN>
  </helper.lighttips>
  <helper.door>
    <FR>Garder votre objectif en vue ne doit pas tourner à l'obsession</FR>
    <EN>Keep your objective in sight but don't become too obsessed with it</EN>
  </helper.door>
  <helper.hiddenkey>
    <FR>L'univers n'a pas à se plier à votre vision du monde pour fonctionner</FR>
    <EN>There's no obligation for the universe to make sense to you</EN>
  </helper.hiddenkey>
  <helper.believe>
    <FR>Si près de la réussite, il faut continuer à y croire</FR>
    <EN>So close to succeed, you need to believe</EN>
  </helper.believe>
  <helper.fail>
    <FR>L'échec est le point de départ du succès</FR>
    <EN>Success always starts with failure</EN>
  </helper.fail>
</data>

